myweddingfavors.com 2006-06-04

# 

_This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please see the[Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/) for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information._ | **My Wedding Favors Privacy Policy** | [](http://www.truste.org/ivalidate.php?url=www.myweddingfavors.com&sealid=101)  
---|---  
  
Your privacy is very important to us. We want to make your experience on the internet as enjoyable and rewarding as possible, and we want you to use the internet’s vast array of information, tools, and opportunities with complete confidence. 

We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy and security. This Privacy Policy describes how My Wedding Favors collects information from all end users of My Wedding Favors' internet services (the "Services") — those who access some of our Services but do not make a purchase ("Visitors") as well as those who make a purchase ("Customers") — what we do with the information we collect, and the choices Visitors and Customers have concerning the collection and use of such information. My Wedding Favors requests that you read this Privacy Policy carefully. 

**Introduction**

My Wedding Favors collects information in different ways from Visitors and customers who access the various parts of our Services. We use this information primarily to provide a customized experience as you use our Services and, generally, do not share this information with third parties. However, we may disclose personal information collected if we have received your permission beforehand or in very special circumstances, such as when we believe that such disclosure is required by law or other special cases described below.

My Wedding Favors collects the following information for purposes of placing an order: name, address, email address, and credit card information. This information allows us to know who and where to ship products to, allows us to email an order confirmation and tracking numbers, and allows us to process the order.

**Access to Personally Identifiable Information**

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, or remove it by emailing our Customer Support at info@myweddingfavors.com or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.

**Data Security**

The membership, bookstore and donations information you provide—including credit card information—is secured using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technology. We use this SSL technology to prevent such information from being intercepted and read as it is transmitted over the Internet. The encrypted data goes to a secure site where your information is stored on restricted-access computers located at restricted-access sites. While we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining this information. Our store is a Yahoo Store, hosted by Yahoo, one of the world's largest providers of secure e-commerce solutions. Please follow the link above for more information on Yahoo's policies.

**Service Providers**

We use other third parties to provide a newsletter on our site. When you sign up for our "Friends List" newsletter, we will share your name and email as necessary for the third party to provide that service. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose, other than allowing us to use their services to send the newsletters to your email address.

**Responses to Email Inquiries**

When Visitors or Customers send email inquiries to My Wedding Favors, the return email address is used to answer the email inquiry we receive. My Wedding Favors does not use the return email address for any other purpose and does not share the return email address with any third party. 

**"Cookies" and My Wedding Favors Uses Them**

A "cookie" is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain Web sites. My Wedding Favors may use cookies to collect, store, and sometimes track information for statistical purposes to improve the products and services we provide and to manage our telecommunications networks. If you are a Customer, we may use a cookie to save your settings and to provide customizable and personalized services. These cookies do not enable third parties to access any of your customer information. Additionally, be aware that if you visit non-My Wedding Favors web sites where you are prompted to log in or that are customizable, you may be required to accept cookies. 

We use third-party tracking services Google Analytics and Clicktracks that use cookies and log files to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate. The information captured is how visitors navigate throughout the site, as well as usage and volume statistics. This information allows us to determine ways that we can improve the site usability, ending it an improved experience for our visitors.

We do/do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

**Choice/Opt-out**

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at privacy(at)myweddingfavors(dot)com, or you may contact us by phone or at the address below to opt-out.

You will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party.

**Special Cases**

It is the policy of My Wedding Favors not to use or share the personal information about Visitors or Customers in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to prohibit such unrelated uses. However, My Wedding Favors may disclose personal information about Visitors or Customers, if we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including: to satisfy laws, such as the Electronic Communications Privacy Act, regulations, or governmental or legal requests for such information; to disclose information that is necessary to operate the Services properly or to protect My Wedding Favors and our Members. 

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

**My Wedding Favors' Commitment to Children's Privacy**

Protecting children’s privacy is especially important to us. It is our policy to comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and all other applicable laws. 

**Smart Marketing, Inc. is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program.**

TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build user’s trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the site http://www.MyWeddingFavors.com . Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Jon Barrett at privacy(at)myweddingfavors(dot)com . If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily address, you should contact TRUSTe at http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php . TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns.

The TRUSTe program does not govern personal information submitted in bulletin boards, chat rooms, or forums. 

**Public Forums**

Please remember that any information you may disclose in our a Discussion Forum, or other public areas of our Web sites or the internet in general, becomes public information. Please exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in these public areas. We are not responsible for users posting personally identifiable information on a public forum.

**Live Chat**

MyWeddingFavors.com uses Live Chat by Liveperson in order to assist our customers online in real-time. It is not neccesary for a user to give out any personal information, although if a user opts to give any personal information to help find an order, that information will be used for that purpose only. 

During the chat, LivePerson Users enter into a live question and answer session with an operator. LivePerson maintains dialogue transcripts of these chats. For more information about LivePerson, and how this information is used/protected, please visit their privacy policy at http://liveperson.com/help/privacy.asp

**Revisions to This Policy**

My Wedding Favors reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy and other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner. Notice of any revision, amendment, or modification will be posted here and will only apply to information collected after any such change. 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage.

**Last Updated on 02/06/2006**

Where to Direct Questions About the My Wedding Favors Privacy Policy 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, contact: 

3012 Adriatic Ct.  
Norcross, GA 30071  
Phone toll free 1-866-942-1311  
Email: privacy(at)myweddingfavors(dot)com
